(Amy:)- Hi.
- Hello.
(Amy:)What are you doing here?
Well, uh, we just wanted to apologize...
(Penny:)...for not bringing you with us
the other day.
(Amy:)That's not necessary.
It's like Sesame Street says:
"One of these things
is not like the others.
One of these things should die alone."
No, come on, Amy,
Iet us make it up to you.
We'll have a girls' night.
We'll do whatever you want.
(Bernadette:)We can go down to the Korean baths
and do that thing...
(Bernadette:)...where we wash each other.
(Penny:)With loofah mitts, no hands.
(Amy:)It's okay. I'm glad this happened.
(Amy:)I can stop pretending
that some beautiful girl...
...and her cute-in-the-right-light friend
wanna hang out with me.
- Amy, we're really sorry.
- Yeah, we feel awful.
(Amy:)Don't. I'll be okay.
(Amy:)You're not the first girls I thought
were friends who ended up shunning me.
(Amy:)It's like elementary school, junior high,
high school, undergrad, grad school...
(Amy:)...and that semester abroad in Norway
all over again.
(Penny:)Oh, come on, Amy.
(Amy:)You don't get it.